A Guide to the James Branch Cabell Collection, 1947-1949
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
James Branch Cabell Collection 1947-1949
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
3210
This collection consists of 12 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was placed on deposit on 1949 April 28.
Arrangement
These are on microfilm (M-221). They are arranged in the order in which they appear on the microfilm. Originals returned to Mr. Bond.
Contents List
- James Branch Cabell to [Nelson] Bond 1949 Mar 18, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1949 Feb 27, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1949 Feb 8, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1949 Jan 27, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Dec 28, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Nov 4, TLS. 1 p.
  [Encl. 1 p. Tms poem beginning, "Item, so that he may abscond..."]
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Oct 7, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Jun 18, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Mar 1, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1948 Jan 2, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1947 Aug 15, TLS. 1 p.
- J.B.C. to Bond 1947 Jul 14, TLS. 1 p.
  [Encl. 1 p. TMs copy for the dust jacket of The Thirty-First of February by Nelson Bond, including statements by J.B.C.]